

PROFILE

I am an organized, analytical and proactive person. I thrive working in a team and I try to add value to every part of the work I do. I always offer solutions to the problems that arise daily, as creativity is one of my strengths.

Thanks to my experience in an international energy company, I'm comfortable working in a big-structured hierarchy.

My great passion is photography. It helps me develop creativity and perceive problems from a different angle.

The quote that could define my attitude towards work is:

"Every problem is a veiled opportunity."

LANGUAGES

Proficient in English and Spanish

SKILLS

Troubleshooting
Data Analysis
Adaptability
Public speaking
Marketing Strategy

CONTACT INFO

LOCATIONS

Prague, Czech Republic Logroño, Spain

PHONE NUMBERS

(+420) 792 914 673 (+34) 699 725 837

E-MAIL

arortega.jobs@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/arturoortega-crespo-14941518b/?locale=en_US

ARTURO ORTEGA CRESPO

Product Owner/Web Services Analyst

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Services Analys and Product Owner - ExxonMobil

January 2022 – Currently working

- Creating and maintaining a product roadmap for enhancements for different Business Units along EAME and Latin America
- Integrate data analysis into daily operations, leveraging insights to inform decision-making and enhance the effectiveness of web services using SQL and Power BI
- Maintaining the product backlog and prioritizing it throughout steady state calls with India team
- Interaction with multiple data providers, development, and marketing teams
- Management of Product Data Sheets (PDS) for Fuels and Lubes products in Global Market using Sitecore (CRM)

International Trade Advisor - Spanish Embassy in Prague

January 2021 - January 2022

- Support and service to Spanish companies for their internationalization process in the Czech Republic
- Market research and partner finding
- Czech Statistical data base management
- Reporting commercial results to ICEX Spain
- Bilateral commerce analysis between Spain and Czech Republic
- International promotion of "Marca España" (Spanish brand)

Email Marketing Analyst - Viewed

February 2020 - September 2020

- Designing email marketing campaigns
- Optimizing customer experience
- CRM management and support to the digital marketing team

Digital Marketing Analyst-Idoneo Mobility

July 2019 - February 2020

- Launching and supervising Facebook Ads campaigns
- Enhancing company's websites
- SEO optimization for company website

EDUCATION

Master's degree in Internationalization of Companies

Economic Development Agency, Spain (ADER) - 2020

Bachelor's Degree in Business Management

University of La Rioja, Spain - 2020 SRH Hochschule Heidelberg, Germany (Erasmus+) - 2018

CERTIFICATIONS

Scrum Master and Product Owner Certification

Udemy - 2023

Proficiency Certificate in English language (C2)

Cambridge University - 2020

ELE (M1) Spanish language teacher certificate

Instituto Cervantes Prague - 2021